(Leonard:)Hey, pretty lady.
(Penny:)You seem extra happy.
(Leonard:)- I guess I am.
- Any particular reason why?
No, just having a good day.
(Leonard:)This morning Sheldon fell asleep
on the way to work...
(Leonard:)...so I got to listen to the radio.
That was crazy.
Mm-hm. Anything else?
(Leonard:)Mm... I found this quiz online called
"Which Star Trek Character Are You?"
(Leonard:)It only took me four tries
to get Captain Kirk. Heh.
- That's great.
- Oh.
(Leonard:)It. Was.
(Penny:)Hmm.
I'm glad you're having such a great day.
(Leonard:)And the one thing that could make it
better is an evening with my special girl.
(Penny:)Oh, and who's that?
(Leonard:)What do you mean?
(Penny:)I just didn't know if you meant me
or Alex.
(Leonard:)Why would I mean Alex?
(Penny:)Because I know she hit on you
and I know you liked it!
(Leonard (jumping and knocking over the Jenga):)What?
(Penny:)Don't play dumb with me,
Ricardo Shilly-Shally!